

MSc. Lukáš Buňát





🎮 Full-Stack Developer 📱 Big Data Engineer 🖓 Business Consultant







+420 731 277 533



bunat.cz



bunatl



lukasbunat

Full-Stack Developer with the primary focus on front-end with 4+ years of experience in web/software development and data science. I have an educational background in Computer Science and Business Informatics at many different universities all over the world. I thrive on multicultural teams and enjoy resolving everyday challenges using my analytical thinking and clever solutions.



Technical Skills

	Front-End	React.js 16.12, JavaScript ES6/2017, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS		
Full-Stack	Back-End	AWS lambda, serverless, Node.js, express.js, apache2, nginx		
technologies	Database	MongoDB (Mongoose, Monk), DynamoDB, MySQL, MS SQL Server		
_	Other	Yarn, npm, circle CI, webpack, parcel, babel, postman		
Data Science	Python, R, Tableu, Rapid Miner, Jupyter, Hive, Spark, Hadoop, PySpark, SQL SSIS/SSAS, BI			
Collaboration	GIT, GitHub, JIRA, Trello, Slack, G Suite, MS Teams, Office 365			



Work Experience



Web developer

09/2019 - Present

Freelancing

Prague, Czech Republic

- I consult businesses to digitalize their processes
- I am implementing (web) automatization tools
- Build and maintain business WordPress websites
- I tutor university students in programming
- Implementing additional web apps' functionalities

Video services specialist

05/2018-05/2019

O2 Czech Republic a.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- I helped to deliver the O2TV platform with 500K users
- **O2TV** is a content streaming platform built with ReactJS and supported with other JAVA SE/EE & C applications
- I integrated an audio/video player for Prague's city hall
- I maintain and develop other internal application
- The platform is available on: https://www.o2tv.cz/

Big Data Analyst

10/2017 - 12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University

Madrid, Spain

- Analyzed Spain's power distribution system to discover consumption patterns using clustering techniques
- Analyzed data were stored in **Hadoop**, I processed them with **Spark** (for faster processing) and I used **Hive** for SQL-like interface. Code is written in PySpark
- The findings (visualized in pandas) allowed to pre-assign the necessary resources in each range of time or season

From 2014 to 2019 I had been working as a volunteer tutor at international student club at CTU.

Featured Projects

Portalo

- A portal that links internal and external web apps into once place. It comes with module managing employees and their information.
- I created project as part of my diploma thesis and distributed it as an open source project
- Front-end part is written in ReactJS with Ant Design and back-end is hosted on AWS with using Lambda, DynamoDB and Cognito services

Czech open data warehouse

- We gather, centralize and structure publicly available data from the Czech administration and transform them into in well-documented and easy-to-use form.
- Processing and historization of mainly financial data records from the Czech public administration
- In collaboration with Open Data Lab

ReactJS 101 projects

- Differences in Redux, useContent and useReducer
- Comparison GraphQL and fetch
- Deployment npm packages

Busines intelligence Company Analysis

- I designed and created a database in MS SQL Server based on structure of raw data.
- I imported raw data, from txt, csv, excel and MS Access, with data pumps using ETL operations in SQL SSIS.
- In SQL SSAS I built OLAP cube and made graphical representation in tableau.





New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic and passionate about learning new things and technologies



Decisiveness and good decision-making (even uder pressure), leadership



Effective time managment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



Education

Unive	rsity, Year(s) of Study	Field of study, Faculty	Location
SE OF PRATE	University of Economics and Business 2019 - Present	Information systems and technologies Graduate (Ing.), exp.06/2021 Faculty of informatics and statistics	Prague, Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University 2019	Open Informatics Faculty of Electrical Engineering	Prague, Czech Republic
(SFS)	University of Finance and Administration 2018-2019	Applied Informatics Undergraduate (Bc.) Faculty of Economics	Prague, Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University 2014–2018	Information Systems and Management Faculty of Information Technology	Prague, Czech Republic
THE PARTY OF THE P	Kyungpook National University 2017	Exchange studies College of IT Engineering	Daegu, South Korea
	Indian Institute of Technology Madras 2016	Exchange studies Department of Computer Science	Chennai, India
NATION OF THE PROPERTY OF THE	Delft University of Technology 2016	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland The ATHENS Programme	P Delft, Netherlands
	Mayflower College of English 2012	Summer language school	Plymouth, United Kingdom



Certificates



CISCO Academy

CCNA 1 (2013)



Autodesk





KFN of UNESCO

Cross Culture Awereness Programme